A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Director of the Department of Historic Resources, 1966-2007
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1966-2007.
  - 1966-2007; Bulk 1990-1999 (Accession 50423)., 17 cu. ft. (17 boxes)
    - Survey and Register, 1994-1995. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Sushella Shanta, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Tax Credit, 2006-2007. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Tax Credit Regulations, 1999. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Tax Credits cats/dogs, 2006 Dec 18. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Tax Forms and Instructions, 1999. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - TEA-21 Funding, 1999/2003. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Teachers Institute, 2000. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Teaching with Historic Places, 1995-2002. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Testimony before Subcommittee, 1996-1998. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Testimony to Advisory Council, 1997. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Jefferson Planning District Commission - Heritage Tourism Toolkit, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Threatened Sites, 1996-1997. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Tides Lodge, Lancaster County, 2003-2004. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Tidewater Regional Office, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Tobacco Commission, 2003-2004. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Tolson, Ed, 1995. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Tourism/Tourism Task Force, Governor Tourism ans Travel Service Advisory Board, 1994-1995. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Transportation Research Board, 2006. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center, 2001-2005. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Trip Folders, 1995-2005. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Trust for Public Lands, 2004-2005. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Trust Leadership Training Interest, 1995-1996. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - 28th Infantry Battle Flag, 2001-2002. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - UK Connection (Calder Loth), 1995. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Under Conferences, 1999. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Underground Railroad, unknown. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Unified Certification Program for Disadvantaged Business, 2003. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - University of Virginia, 2001. (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - University Press of Virginia, 1995. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1998. (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Urban Policy Working Group, 1995. (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Urofsky, et al. Governor Allen, 1997. (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Association of Counties (VACO), 1994-1995. (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Association of Museums, 1997-2005. (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Antebellum Iron Industry - Multiple Property Documentation, 1995. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Civil Rights in Education Heritage Trail, 2004 May 14. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1994-2005. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Cultural Network Work Plan, 2000. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation, 1994-1996. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities, 1994. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Virginia History Initiative, 1995-1997. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Committee Listings, 1996. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Virginia History Initiative Finale/Toolkits, 1997-1999. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Vermont Meeting 1994 July. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Housing Study Commission 2000 Annual Report, 2000-2001. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Virginia History Initiative Focus Group Meetings, 1996. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Virginia History Initiative, 1998 Jan 8. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Virginia History Initiative, 1998. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Virginia History Initiative - steering Committee, Chip Mann, Financing Tools, 1997. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Housing Study Commission, 1999-2000. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Valentine Richmond History Center, 2007. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Valley Conservation Council, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Association of Museums - List, 1999. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Museum and Historical Sites - General, 1996. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Museum and Sites - Marketing, 1996. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Natural and Historic Resources Fund, 2004. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Virginia commonwealth University - Architectural History Symposium, 2002-2004. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Background, 1993-1995. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Economic Impact, 1993-1995. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Virginia History Initiative - inception, 1994-1995. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Master File, 1994-1998. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Organization and Plenary, 1995-1996. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Plenary Session, 1995-1996. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Preservation Partners, 1996. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Sponsors, 1995-1996. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Virginia History Initiative - State Agency Group, 1996. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Steering Committee, 1996. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Charles Bryan, 1998. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Commending Correspondence, 1996-1999. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Department of Historic Resources Internal Correspondence, 1995-1996. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Lease Agreement/Legislative Actions, 1995. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Letters to VHS from the Department of Historic Resources, 1995-1998. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Outside Correspondence, 1994-1999. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Public Relations, 1995. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Historical Society - Staff Notes, 1995-1996. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Archaeology Month, 2002. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Archaeology Plan, 2001. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Agricultural Reserve Program, 1995. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Capitol Preview Gala, 2007. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Capital Trail, 2005. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Capital Consortium, undated. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Center for Architecture, 2005. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Council on Indians 2001/2004. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Environmental Assembly - Virginia Conservation Network, 2002-2004. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Environmental Endowment, 1997/2004. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Executive Institute, 2006. (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Executive Institute, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Forest Stewardship Coordinating Committee, 2002. (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Virginia History Initiative - Survey, 1987/1988; 1996/1997. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Home for Boys, 1995. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Horse Center, 2003. (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Indians, 2003-2004. (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Institute Political Leadership Education, 1996/2000. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Land and Conservation Foundation, 2001-2006. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Landmark and National Register Listings, 1991-2001. (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Main Street Program Managers, 1999-2005. (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2003-2005. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute, 1997-2005. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1994-2004. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Museum Of Natural History, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation, 2003-2005. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Performing Arts Foundation, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Preservation Conference, 1998. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Preservation Foundation, 1997-1999. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Properties, 1996. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Settler's Monument, 1997. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Virginia State Library, 1994. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Virginia State Parks Foundation, 2003. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Virginia's Sustainable Future, 1999. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Tech, 1994. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Tourism Conference, 1995. (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2001-2006. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Women, 2001-2002. (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Vision 20/10, 2000. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Visitor Registration Books, 1998. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - VITA Contract, 2003. (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - V Trans 2025, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - VISITVA - Tourism, 1996. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Volunteer, 1995. (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Wage Employee - Hiring Request, 1996. (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Mary Washington College, 2002-2004. (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Washington - Rochambeau Revolutionary Route, 2004-2005. (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Weanack Land LLP Gravel Pit Tract (Charles City County), 2004. (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Weeks, Ross, 1994-1995. (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Welfare Reform Program, 1995. (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Weekly Reports Format, undated (about 1995). (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Whitehurst/Buffington, Newport News, Virginia, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Winchester Regional Office, 1995-1997. (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Wise County Historical Society, 1996. (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Woodrow Wilson Bridge, 1997-2000. (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - World Monuments Fund, undated. (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Worsham Street Bridge, City of Danville, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Year 2000, 1997-1999. (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Work Plan, 1994-1998. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Y2K Rollover, 1999-2000. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Yorktown Riverwalk, 2004-2005. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Yorktown Shipwreck Archaeology, 1996. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Young Leader Conference, 1994-1995. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Zirkle Mill, Forestville, (Shenandoah County, Virginia), 2004-2005. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (including NCSHPO), 1997-1998. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HPF Reauthorization to 2004, 1998. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Heritage Foundation, 1996. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Virginia History Initiative: William and Mary Focus Group, 1996. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Virginia History Initiative: Membership Drive, 1996. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Virginia History Initiative: Overheads for Presentation, 1996. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Renovations - Executive Mansion, 1998. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (including Agency Accomplishments), 1995-1999. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Code of Virginia and Preservation Law Reporter, Historic Preservation, 1994. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - ACHP Proposal, 1995. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1994-2000. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - ARB Problem, 1994. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Alliance Review, 1997. (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous: Publications and Documents, Press Releases, etc., 1996-1996. (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Archaeology Commission), 1993-1999. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Virginia History Initiative, 1995-1996. (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Strategic Plan - 1999, 1997-1999. (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Office Systems Task Force, 1998. (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - GIS Clearing House Legislation, 1997. (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 1997-1998. (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1994. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1995. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Sample Joint Project Agreements, 2003-2004. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Samples, 1994-1997. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Session Issues, 1997. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Proposals, 1993-1997. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Buck Slip, 1999. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Buck Slips, 1998. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Buck Slips, 1997. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Allen/Gilmore Transition, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Technology, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - August, 1996. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - September, 1996. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - October, 1996. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - November, 1996. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - December, 1996. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - January, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - February, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - March, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - April, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - May, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - June, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - July, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - August, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - September, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - October, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - November, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - December, 1997. (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - January, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - February, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - March, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - April, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - May, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - June, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - July, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - August, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - September, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - October, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - November, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Benefits of Preservation, 1999-2000. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Biennial Reports - Strategic Planning, 1997. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1994-1996. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - December, 1998. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - January, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - February, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - March, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - April, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - May, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - June, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - July, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - August, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - September, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - October, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - November, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - December, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - January, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - February, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - March, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - April, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - May, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - June, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - July, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - August, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - September, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - October, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - November, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - December, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - 51st National Preservation Conference, 2000. (Box 44, Folder 29)